Facilities and Physical Plant, Office of; Records ua331
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of Facilities Management2004 April 4 - 2017 May 17
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Office of Equipment Management
ua331
11 268 Captures
The collection consists of inactive records from the University at Albany's Office of Facilities Management.
Collection X
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Biographical History
The University at Albany's Office of Facilities Management is a unit within the Division of Finance and Business organized with 6 major departments: Campus Planning; Architecture, Engineering, and Construction Management; Maintenance and Operations; Energy Management; Environmental Health and Safety and Administrative Services.
Scope and Contents
The collections consists of University at Albany Office of Facilities Management records including budget files, 198386; and subject files for the office which includes several constituent bodies, including: Real Estate, Physical Plant Department (including Residence Hall Maintenance and Utilities Branch, HVAC), Fiscal Management, Environmental Health and Safety, Facilities Acquisition, Building and Institutional Services, Downtown Campus Operations, Pest Control, and the Vehicle Operations Center.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. While it is likely that portions of the collection may be viewed, access must be managed by an archivist.
Architecture; Web Archives; UAlbany Finance & Business; Wages -- New York (State); State University of New York at Albany-Office of Facilities Management
- Office of Facilities Management Website, 2004 April 4 - 2017 May 17; 1; 268 captures
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/facilities/
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: University at Albany, SUNY Website
  created_date: 2012-09-17T13:15:00Z
  created_by: bkeough
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:05Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2004 April 4
    Scope and Contents
    Meta tag for description: Maintains the campus academic buildings, internal mechanical equipment, and campus streets & external surfaces. Coordinates & provides technical & design services for all campus construction & renovation. Maintains all official campus mapping. Maintains detailed archives concerning the specs & histories of our buildings & grounds.
    Meta tag for author: Robert Mergen
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2004 June 4
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2004 August 18
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2004 September 23
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2004 October 18
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 February 4
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 March 10
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 September 9
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 September 14
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 September 17
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 September 23
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 October 20
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 October 31
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2005 November 12
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2006 February 20
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2006 May 10
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2006 June 29
  - University at Albany - Office of Facilities Management, 2006 August 23
  - Office of University Facilities Operations, 2007 April 8
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2007 October 30
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2007 December 1
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2008 January 1
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2008 February 3
    Meta tag for keywords: We are a unit within the Division of Finance and Business. Our six major departments are Architecture, Engineering, and Construction Management, Space Management and Campus Preservation, Physical Plant and Facility Services, Administrative Services, Energy Management, and Information Technology. The Office of Facilities Management also provides campus customers with service for special events, grounds, maintenance, and craft-specific services. We maintain all official campus mapping and detailed archives concerning the specifications and history of our buildings and grounds.
    Meta tag for description: We are a unit within the Division of Finance and Business. Our six major departments are Architecture, Engineering, and Construction Management, Space Management and Campus Preservation, Physical Plant and Facility Services, Administrative Services, Energy Management, and Information Technology. The Office of Facilities Management also provides campus customers with service for special events, grounds, maintenance, and craft-specific services. We maintain all official campus mapping and detailed archives concerning the specifications and history of our buildings and grounds.
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2008 May 9
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2009 January 25
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2009 January 31
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2010 February 17
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2010 April 19
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2010 May 27
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2010 June 22
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2010 September 27
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2011 February 14
  - Office of Facilities Management, 2011 August 4
    Meta tag for keywords: University at Albany, Facilities Management
    Meta tag for description: The Facilities Department provides campus customers with service for special events, grounds, maintenance, and craft-specific services, as well as campus mapping and building archives.
    Meta tag for author: Robert Mergen, overhauled by Devin Fortman
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2011 October 10
    Meta tag for keywords: SUNY, suny Albany, Facilities Management
    Meta tag for description: Information about the University at Albany's Office of Facilities Management
    Meta tag for author: Devin Fortman
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 January 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 March 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 May 14
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 July 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 July 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 July 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 September 4
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 November 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2012 December 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 January 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 January 19
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 February 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 February 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 February 24
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 March 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 April 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 8
    This item had no crawl rules.
    The CDX index for this capture did not contain crawl information.
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 8
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 8
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 8
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 15
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 15
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 22
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 22
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 29
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 May 29
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 5
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 12
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 12
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 19
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 19
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 26
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 June 26
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 17
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 24
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 24
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 31
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 July 31
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 14
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 14
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 21
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 21
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 28
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 August 28
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 4
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 4
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 11
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 25
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 25
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 September 30
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 2
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 16
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 16
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 30
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 October 30
  - Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2013 November 13
  - WARC file for Internet Archive Wayback Machine, 2013 November 13
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 November 20
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 November 20
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 11
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 18
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 18
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 25
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2013 December 25
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 1
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 15
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 15
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 22
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 22
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 29
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 January 29
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 12
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 12
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 19
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 19
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 26
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 February 26
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 March 5
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 March 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 March 26
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 March 26
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 2
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 9
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 9
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 23
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 April 23
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 6
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 7
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 7
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 21
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 21
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 28
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 May 28
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 4
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 4
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 11
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 18
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 June 18
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 2
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 9
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 9
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 16
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 16
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 23
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 23
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 30
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 July 30
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 6
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 6
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 20
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 20
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 27
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 August 27
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 3
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 3
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 10
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 10
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 17
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 September 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 1
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 22
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 22
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 29
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 October 29
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 November 5
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 November 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 November 19
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 November 19
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 December 24
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 December 24
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 December 30
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 December 31
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2014 December 31
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 January 7
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 January 7
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 January 14
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 January 14
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 February 4
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 February 4
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 February 11
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 February 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 March 11
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 March 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 March 25
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 March 25
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 15
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 15
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 22
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 22
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 29
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 April 29
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 6
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 6
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 13
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 13
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 20
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 20
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 27
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 May 27
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 3
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 3
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 10
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 10
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 17
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 June 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 July 17
    crawl: 165088